is 5.
disclaimer we are not suggesting any
stock to buy or sell this video for
education and informative purpose only
please consider your financial advisor
before making any decision
you could occurs limited share price 93
52 week high 93 rupees 52 week low 22
rupees time market cap micro cap penny
stocks or risk is that bonus one issue
two one bonus two share held they
already declare recorded now their
reviser recorded now the new record
dated 3 October it's date may be 30
September
career facility and service limited
service 29 rupees 40 price 40 rupees 52
week load 12 rupees physically rupees 10
market cap micro cap where every penny
stocks are very risk is there bonus one
is to one one bonus for everyone Cheryl
recorded 12 October X date may be 11
October
industry limited share price
60 rupees 72 52 week low 6 rupees 40
paise
if you have one share you get six bonus
share
record it will be 5 October X date may
be 3 October this is rarely State stocks
so we cannot buy the stock easily the
last trade was happened in 2010. today
video bonus tracks are not trading
regularly very rarely trade strong
please note that
all the bonus three stocks
upcoming board of directors meeting May
consider dividend and bonus
please note may consider there is no any
guarantee
Ram Krishna forging limited share price
176 52 week high
252 52 week low 145 phases rupees 10
Rupees to market cap small cap board
meeting scheduled to be held on 21st
October may consider second interim
dividend also declaring result Financial
result
is there
board meeting scheduled to be held on 4
October may consider bonus ratio
if any
order received by Leicester company
there is one company give a taken very
good order
alicon cash Loy limited share price 176
market cap small cap
this is information that the company is
selected by Jaguar Land Rover UK to
supply EXL housing a critical product
for its immobility platform the
manufacturing of EXL
using will be Tinder taken by the
company is plant at Pune Maharashtra
the amount of the order is not declared
but they got very good order from Jaguar
Land Rover UK United Kingdom
that's for all thanks for watching